乔 拿着这根球杆 把那颗球打出去
Okay, Joey, you take this club, and you hit that ball.
有问题吗
Any questions?
为什么这上面写着"曼尼"
Why does this say "Manny"?
别在意 他只用过一次
Don't worry about it. They were only used once.
算是我与他的一次"挥杆落空"经历
It was a swing and a miss for both of us.
我得想个新方式和乔共度美好时光
I needed to find a way to spend more quality time with Joe.
周六捉迷藏我实在玩不下去了
I couldn't take another Saturday of hide-and-seek.
玩到现在 我藏在"柜子"里的时间
At this point, I've spent more time
已经比米奇尔还久了
in the closet than Mitchell.
高尔夫是非常复杂的运动
Golf is a very complicated sport.
你打不到也别泄...
I don't want you to get frustrated if you don't --
天啊
Holy cow!
你觉得你能再来一次吗
Do you think you can do that again?
能 很简单
Yeah. It's easy.
行了 自大狂先生
Okay, Mr. Cocky.
这世上有种情况叫新手的好...
You know, there is a thing called beginner's --
什么鬼
What the hell?
布雷迪
Hey, Brady.
杰 你好吗 这是你孙子吗
Hey, Jay, what's up? Oh, is this your grandson?
这话我听够了 这是我儿子
I can't do this again. This is my son.
看看他挥杆告诉我你怎么想
Just take a look at his swing and tell me what you think.
你妈妈肯定是名优秀运动员
Your mom must be some athlete.
提醒你一下 我这人特别不喜欢
Just so you know, I'm not a guy who's charmed
服务员跟我自来熟
when the help gets familiar.
大家今早都过得好吗
How's everybody this fine morning?
我的新年决意已经坚持了三天
Welp, I'm on my third day of my New Year's Resolution
我不说别人不在乎的话
to not say things nobody cares about.
失误了
Damn it.
业主协会的回复
Oh, yay, Homeowners Association.
我需要他们批准我在后院盖女人窝
I need their approval to put a She Shed in the backyard
就是过去放跷跷板那块地
where the teeter-totter used to be.
我没听懂
I don't understand.
她说女人窝"做"在跷跷板上
She said, "She Shed down by the seesaw."
您的才华怎么会埋没至今
How are you not famous?
是啊 真有才 但女人窝是什么
Yes, bravo, but what's a She Shed?
就是个简单的小棚子
Well, it's just a simple little structure
让我可以自己静静
where I can go to be alone
做做瑜伽或冥想 不受旁人打扰
and do yoga or meditate and nobody can bother me.
这么说在浴缸里喝红酒抽雪茄
Oh, so a glass of wine and a cigarette in the tub
已经不管用了
isn't cutting it anymore?
我不抽烟 宝贝 那是烟草味的香烛
I don't smoke, honey. I have a tobacco-scented candle.
哪有烟草味的...
They don't make tobacco-scented --
你说的这些就是没人在乎的话
This is more of that stuff no one cares about.
恭喜你 亲爱的
Congratulations, honey.
别假装替我高兴了
Don't pretend you're happy for me.
卢克和我想用那块地盖击球场
Luke and I wanted to use that space to put in a batting cage.
克莱尔想要她的女人窝
Claire wanted her She Shed.
我们陷入了僵局
We were in a stalemate,
于是我们像成年人一样解决矛盾
so we settled the dispute like adults.
加油 老爸 想想击球场
Come on, Dad. Batting cage.
我真的很需要眨眼 伙计
I really need to blink, buddy.
你去世以后可以眨个够
You can blink when you're dead.
太棒了
Ah, yes! Yes!
当年那些三维立体画海报没白看
All those Magic Eye posters paid off.
我要给自己买块毛绒绒的小地毯
I'm gonna get myself one of those fuzzy little rugs.
-他们没批准 -什么
- They turned me down. - ?What?
他们到底为什么...
Why on Earth would they do th-
我要想办法联系上
I-I'm gonna find out how to get in touch with somebody
那个业主协会里的某个人
from down at that Homeowners Association
弄清楚到底怎么回事
and find out what the hell is going on.
克莱尔 我知道你很生气
Claire, I know you're upset,
但我不认为你该那么做
but I don't think you should do that.
瞧瞧啊
Well, look at that.
他们今天下午正好要开会
They have a meeting this afternoon.
我亲自去一趟
I'll just go down there in person.
亲爱的 我有好多客户是业主协会推荐的
Honey, I get a lot of my referrals from the HOA.
和他们疏远了得不偿失
We can't afford to alienate them.
是他们要疏远别人
They are the ones who are alienating people.
他们都住在那个死胡同里
They all live on that stupid cul-de-sac.
只为自己人行方便
They only do things for each other.
如果他们不是都丑得要命没准会搞大群交
Probably swing if they weren't so aggressively unattractive.
我觉得"女人窝"这个叫法很冒犯人
You know, I find the term "She Shed" offensive.
为什么不管女人的窝叫窝
Shouldn't ours just be called a shed
而男人的叫"男人窝"
and theirs a "He Shed"?
你的新年决意是白决的吗
Why do you bother making resolutions?
真让人泄气
This is so frustrating.
如果这话能安慰到你
If it's any comfort...
你不是唯一因为他们不如意的人
...you're not the only one to be stung by these people.
他们离谱的停车规定让我放弃了
Their ridiculous parking regulation made me give up my dream
买车顶有大热狗的车的梦想
of owning the Oscar Mayer Wienermobile.
好吧 我放手
Fine. I will move on.
这意味着我们能搭击球场了吗
So does this mean we can get our batting cage?
卢克 让人家缓缓
Luke, too soon.
没错 快走
Yes. Go.
我真为你骄傲 老妈
I'm really proud of you, Mom.
放手体现了你的成熟
Letting go shows real growth.
我要去业主协会的会议
I'm going to that Homeowners Association meeting,
我的女人窝肯定要盖
and I'm getting my She Shed.
但你刚刚告诉老爸...
But you just told Dad --
我默允他表演魔术
I let him do magic.
他默允我打破承诺
He lets me break promises.
我们都知道彼此是什么样的人
We both know what we married.
你们又去球场了
You were at the course again?
这周每天上午都去
That's every morning this week.
冠军就是这么练出来的
That's how you make a champion.
你该看看乔的本事
You should see Joe play.
就像看名主持梅夫·格里芬采访一样
It's like watching Merv Griffin interview.
独有一套技巧
There's a certain finesse to it.
-你在训练什么项目 -啥也没练
- What are you training for? - Nothing.
没错 那就去吃布丁
Yeah, then go have a pudding cup.
这些高能蛋白质棒是精英运动员吃的
These high-performance protein bars are for elite athletes.
吃吧 乔 补充能量
Go ahead, Joey. Fuel up.
你今天有座奖杯要赢
You have a trophy to bring back today.
你这话是什么意思
What are you talking about?
俱乐部办了场儿童锦标赛
There's a kiddie tournament up at the club,
我帮乔报名了
and I signed Joe up for it.
杰 你把他逼得太紧了
Jay, you're pushing him too hard.
你胡说什么 孩子可喜欢了
What are you talking about? Kid loves it.
等他冰敷好肩膀亲口告诉你
He'll tell you himself after he ices his shoulder.
就是这个感觉
Ooh, that's the stuff.
歌洛莉亚 如果训练得当
You know, Gloria, with the right training,
这孩子能一路走到顶峰
this kid could go all the way.
当他的高尔夫生涯经理就是我的第二春
Me managing his golf career can be my second act.
你都七十了 你的第四春都该过劲了
You're 70. Your second act was two acts ago.
别利用他再次感受青春 他压力太大
Stop living through him. It's too much pressure.
你为什么这么小题大做
Why are you making such a big deal about it?
不过是个儿童高尔夫锦标赛
It's a-It's a kiddie golf tournament.
就像个我不抗拒参加的儿童玩耍聚会
It's like a-a playdate I don't hate being at.
这是个馊主意
It's a bad idea.
如果乔想做竞争性不这么强的事呢
What if Joe wants to do something that is less competitive,
例如阅读或纸模
like reading or papier-mache?
我们先别把曼尼那套剧本都拿出来
Let's not break out the Manny playbook just yet.
叫戏单更有范 我帮什么嘴
Playbill would've been more cutting. Why am I helping you?
我知道关于什么对乔最好
I know you think you have the monopoly
你认为你有垄断权
on deciding what's best for Joe,
但我也有父母的天性
but I have parenting instincts, too.
过去米奇和克莱尔的事我都让迪迪说了算
I deferred to Dede every single time on Mitch and Claire,
这次我要按我的直觉办
and this time I'm going with my gut.
米奇和克莱尔现在不是很好吗
Mitch and Claire turned out to be wonderful people.
是的是的 我不是说他们不好
Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm not knocking them.
我对所有孩子的爱都是平等的
I love all my children equally.
这是冠军喝的水
That's winner water.
怎么回事 小卡
What's going on, Cam?
我才离开四十五分钟
I was gone for 45 minutes,
咱家客厅就变成了美容沙龙
and now our living room's a beauty salon?
难不成你有一队[赛车]专业技师吗
What, do you have a pit crew or something?
你居然挺有男人样地
Ooh, look at you using "pit crew"
用"专业技师"成功造句了
in a sentence like a boy.
这都是为了莉莉的派对吗 你...
Is this all for Lily's party? You --
我以为我们的计划是吃披萨看电影
I thought we were just gonna do pizza and a movie.
要来的可是一帮十二岁少女
Okay, there are 12-year-old girls coming over here.
你忘了海莉在那年纪多毒舌多爱评头论足吗
Do you remember how mean and judgmental Haley was at that age?
记得 逼得我在感恩节装病
Yeah, I faked being sick that Thanksgiving.
我都不敢在她面前吃玉米
I was too scared to eat corn in front of her.
你当然不敢
Of course you were.
那一整年她对我说的唯一一个词是"恶心"
The only word she said to me that entire year was "Ew."
总之 莉莉想给这些学姐留个好印象
Anyway, Lily wants to impress these older girls,
于是我弄了全方位沙龙帮她们大改造
so I set up a full-service salon to do makeovers.
你拥有这个资格是因为...
And you're qualified to do that because...?
我叔叔就是干这行的
Okay, my uncle was in the business
他让骡子看起来更年轻好卖出去
of mules appear younger for sale,
所以我认为我对美发和化妆略知一二
so I think I know a thing or two about hair and make-up.
我拿了些东西来帮莉莉的派对做准备
I brought y'all some stuff for Lily's party.
我的天
Oh, my God.
我想你可能不愿意用自己的护肤品
Thought you might not want to get into your own stash.
我知道你的贵妇面霜有多贵
I know how pricy your lady creams are.
她发脾气是因为我继承了老妈的皮肤
Okay, she's lashing out because I inherited Mama's skin.
-而我继承了老爸的弹脑门绝招 -别
- And I got Daddy's strong flickin' finger. - Don't do it! Don't!
小卡 你说过你不会搞得太大的
Cam, you said that you were gonna keep this small.
你瞧 我觉得你故意不告诉我
See, now I feel like you didn't tell me about this
好在我拒绝前把这些都弄好
so that you could set it all up before I could say no.
你这话可说错了
Okay, that is just not true.
不是每个人都像你想得心机那么深
Not everyone is as calculating as you think.
但 我知道你为什么这样
But, hey, I know where this is coming from,
这不是你的错
and it's not your fault.
真的假的 又来这套
Seriously? This again?
这似乎是私人话题
This sounds private.
如果你想让我回避 想都别想
If you want me to leave, forget it.
好吧 我们每次起了争执
Okay, a-any time we have an argument,
小卡都说是我童年阴影的错
Cam blames it on how I was brought up.
我的心理咨询师说
My therapist says
这是他转移责任的方式
that it's his way of deflecting responsibility.
你去做心理咨询
You go to therapy?
像伍迪·艾伦的电影里演得那样吗
You mean like one of those Woody Allen movies?
很多人都做心理咨询
Plenty of people go to therapy.
我们农场人就不去
Not farm folk.
我们有问题自己解决 尤其我们问题也不多
We solve our own problems, not that we had many.
没错 因为你们的童年像故事书里一样
That's right, because you had a storybook childhood.
我可没说过"故事书" 不过有一次
I never said "storybook," although one time
我回家时的确看到一家熊在吃我们的粥
I did come home to a family of bears eating our porridge.
别说得好像我们是乡巴佬一样
Don't make us sound like hicks.
是微波炉意面
It was Tuna Helper.
但我们也有过烦恼
But we did have our share of problems.
烦恼 什么烦恼
Problems? What problems?
老妈和老爸啊
Mama and Daddy?
他们的婚姻又不完美
It's not like they had the perfect marriage.
谢谢你 谢谢你
Thank you. Thank you.
我就知道有阴影 人人都有阴影
I knew there was stuff. Everybody has stuff.
不 没有阴影
No, there is no stuff.
她在编故事想气皱我容光焕发的皮肤
She's just making this up to get under my radiant skin.
如果你不知道我在说什么
If you don't know what I'm talking about,
我可不想在你主持大型派对前告诉你
I'm not gonna tell you right before you host a big ol' party.
不 我们有时间 快说给我们听听
Oh, no, no. We've got time. Come on, come on. Let's hear it.
你不记得有次老爸离开我们一整年
You don't remember that time Daddy didn't live with us for a year
因为他和那个餐厅服务员同居了吗
'cause he was shacked up with that diner waitress
-珍妮·苏·巴特勒 -拜托
- Jannie Sue Butler? - Oh please.
老爸唯一离开我们那次是去参战了
The only time Daddy ever left was to go to war.
1977年哪来的战争 小卡
It was 1977. What war, Cam?
越...
The V-
他离开我们是因为他到了四十岁
He left us 'cause he turned 40,
脸上长了第一块老年斑
he got his first liver spot,
他又觉得那骚货像《无敌女金刚》
and that bimbo reminded him of the Bionic Woman --
主要是因为她有条假胳膊
mostly on account of her fake arm.
你是真的不知情吗
Oh, did you really not know this?
什么
What?
我没意识到会是这么严重的问题
I did not realize how big that was gonna be.
小卡 你还好吧
Cam, hey. Y-You're okay, right?
小卡 我自己应付不来这些十二岁少女
Cam, I-I-I can't face these 12-year-olds by myself.
十二岁 我得去换件衣服
12-year-olds? I got to change my shirt.
她们已经生气了
They're already angry.
好吧
Um, okay. Uh...
你们在做什么
What are you guys doing?
-搭击球场 -小心
- Putting up our batting cage. - Oh, careful.
这些网特别容易缠住脚
It's really easy to get caught in the net.
你们或许想先缓缓
Okay, well, you may want to take a beat.
老妈去业主协会争取女人窝了
Mom went down to the HOA meeting to fight for her shed.
我只希望她能冷静地接受他们的决定
?I only hope she keeps her cool and accepts their decision.
是啊 鉴于她以往总能放手的优秀历史
Yeah, based on her long history of letting things go.
爸 我们有麻烦了
Dad, we have a problem.
或许没事 伙计 业主协会从不反悔
Maybe not, buddy. The HOA never reverses itself.
要不然我们这场对话
If they did, we'd be having this conversation
就能在大热狗车的前座上说了
in the front seat of a giant hot dog.
-我就是业主协会 -什么
- I am the HOA. - ?What?
我截住了老妈的申请
I intercepted Mom's application
假造了一封协会的回绝信
and forged a rejection letter from the board.
-为什么 -因为你叫我那么做的
- Why?! ?- Because you told me to.
我什么时候叫你那么做的
When did I tell you to do that?!
太棒了
Ah, yes! Yes!
当年那些三维立体画海报没白看
All those Magic Eye posters paid off!
真闹心
This sucks.
谁知道
Who knows?
或许业主协会会拒绝她的申请
Maybe the HOA board will reject her application.
船到桥头自然直
Things have a way of working themselves out.
你说的是我想的吗
Are you saying what I think you're saying?
应该是
I think so.
-你给了我暗示 -什么暗示
- You gave me the signal. - What signal?!
就你想让我秘密解决某事的时候那个眨眼
That wink when you want me to secretly take care of something.
我当然得眨眼 我刚结束瞪眼比赛
Of course I was winking. I was just in a staring contest.
什么 你是说你以前也这么做过吗
Wait. Did you say you've done this before?
你觉得艾丽克斯的大提琴会自燃嘛
Do you think Alex's cello set itself on fire?
天啊
Oh, my God.
我得赶到那个大会 趁你妈还没...
I got to get down to that meeting before your mother --
快帮我解开
Untangle me quickly!
等下 你在眨眼吗
Wait. Was that a wink?
你不想我帮你解开吗
Do you not want me to untangle you?
还是你想我解慢点
D-Do you want me to untangle you slowly?
没有暗示
There's no signal!
清爽的黄瓜水 不喝吗
Refreshing cucumber water? No?
-你渴... -你做得很棒
- Are you thirs-- - Hey, you're doing great.
就是别紧张 别脸红
Just don't get nervous and turn all red.
我脸红啦 我现在脸红了吗
Do I do that? Am I doing that right now?
其他人注意到了吗
Do people notice?
你不是12岁了 没事
Okay, you're not 12. It's okay.
变好了 变好了
It got better. It got better.
小卡 你怎么样
Hey, Cam. H-How you feeling?
如果你需要时间
If you need some time to
来消化有关父亲的事 你...
process that stuff about your dad, y-you sh--
不 我没事
Oh, no. I'm fine.
不像梅勒妮头发上的氯
Unlike the chlorine in Melanie's hair
那事不会有什么永久性伤害的
that won't do any permanent damage.
我在干活呢 亲爱的
I'm working here, sweetie.
姑娘们 我是莉莉的酷姑姑
Hi, girls. I'm Lily's cool Aunt Pam.
我给大家带了打火机哦
I brought lighters for everyone.
对我好点
Please be nice.
好了 完成啦 你觉得怎么样
All right. We are done. What do you think?
我是要当红歌手赛琳娜·戈麦斯的发型
I wanted to look like Selena Gomez.
我还想我爸遵守结婚誓言呢
Oh, well, I wanted a daddy that would respect his wedding vows,
但我们不能总是得到我们想要的
but we can't all get what we want.
现实点吧 去吧
Dream smaller. There you go.
好了 就是这些话
Okay, okay. See, it's stuff like that
让我觉得你其实在难过
that makes me think that you're not okay.
米奇尔 是玩笑 理发店专属吐槽
Mitchell, it's just a joke. It's barbershop sass.
他们喜欢我这么说
They love it when I go there.
好啦 维奥莱 挪动你的高档屁股来
All right, Violet, get your fancy can in the chair.
到你了
You're up.
你想做成什么样的
Hi. So, what are we doing today?
我想要盘发
I was thinking of an updo.
你还是来个高马尾吧
I like a high pony for you.
开始啦
There we go.
小维啊 我在父母之夜上见了你妈
Oh, so, Vi, I've seen your mom at Parent Night.
你知道吗 我从没见过你爸
You know what? I've never seen your dad.
他经常加班
He works late a lot.
宝贝 希望这是真的
Well, I hope that's true, sweetie.
为什么不是真的
Why wouldn't it be?
不知道 有时父亲会撒谎
I don't know. Sometimes father's lie.
现在发现会比
It's better for you to find out now
你已经40岁时才发现要好
than when you're a 40-year-old man.
40 说到父亲撒谎
40? Okay, speaking of fathers lying.
我能和你聊下吗
Can I talk to you for a second?
小卡 走 走
Cam, move away, move away.
-小卡 你很明显在不开心嘛 -好吧
- Cam -- Cam, clearly you're not okay. - Okay, you know what?
我以为我能压下去 关进房间并锁好
I thought -- I thought I could tamp it down, put it in a room,
就像爷爷的狂犬病时我们做的那样
seal it shut just like we did grandpa when he got rabid.
听着 我和我的咨询师打过招呼了
Okay, listen, I-I may have checked with my therapist
如果你想和人谈谈...
on the off chance that you would want to talk to someone.
不
No, sir.
一旦我开了那扇门 很难预料到会发现什么
If I open that door, there's no telling what we'll find.
你知道我听到那首歌《调情圣手》时
You know what? I -- You know I cry inexplicably
就会莫名其妙哭起来吗
when I hear "Smooth Operator."
我不想知道那是为什么
I don't want to know what that's about.
就试一下
Hey, hey, just -- just give it a shot.
她很棒的 如果
Yeah, she's the best, and if --
如果你感到不舒服 我们就走 好吗
if it makes you uncomfortable, we can leave, all right?
她今天下午有时间
She -- She has an opening this afternoon.
如果聚会还没结束呢
What if the party's still going on?
你姐在这 不会有事的
Your sister's here. They'll be fine.
真心话
Okay, truth.
你第一次亲吻男生是多大
How old were you when you first kissed a boy?
男的 人吗
Hmm...A boy person?
我喜欢你回家
I love that you're here,
但你们学校不是有洗衣房吗
but don't you guys have a laundry room at the school?
那里很潮湿
It's really humid down there,
我的头发可无法承受
and my hair is challenging enough as it is.
我还以为你会去看乔的比赛
I thought you'd be going to Joe's tournament.
不 他不需要我
No, he doesn't need me over there.
我只会增加压力
I would be adding more pressure.
你在我的丝带舞比赛上
Well, you always kept a low profile
就总是很低调啊
at my ribbon-dancing competitions.
我在看台上都找不到你
I couldn't even find you in the stands.
对 有丝带还有嗖嗖嗖的声音
Ah, yeah, with the ribbon and the swooshing.
但乔让我担心 因为压力会摧毁孩子
But Joe worries me because stress can destroy a child.
我从我们地区青少年仰泳比赛中得到的教训
Take it from Cartagena's junior regional backstroke champion.
你还会游泳吗
You used to swim?
就像到公海躲条子的快艇一样快
Like a cigarette boat fleeing to international waters.
但压力唤醒我心中的黑暗
But all that stress brought the darkness in me.
我开始抓狂 然后发生了意外
I started pulling out my hair, and...there was an incident.
什么意外
What kind of incident?
我羞于承认
I'm ashamed to admit it,
但我输了一场重要的比赛后
but when I lost one of the big races,
我貌似用了泳池捞叶网
I might have hit one of the other swimmers
砸了其他选手的腿
in the leg with a skimmer pole.
你对别的姑娘使出了"坦雅·哈丁"吗
You Tonya Harding-ed another girl?
不 在哥伦比亚 这招名叫"歌洛莉亚·拉米雷兹"
No, in Colombia, they call it the Gloria Ramirez-ing.
妈 你崩溃了不代表乔也会
Mom, just because you freaked out doesn't mean Joe will.
说到底
At the end of the day,
他以后只会记得你没去看比赛
he's only going to remember that you weren't there.
我不知道
I don't know.
我觉得会对他意义很重大
I think it would mean a lot to him.
就像你当年为我和搭档加油
I know it meant a lot to me
对我来说也意义非凡一样
when you cheered on me and my ribbon-dancing partner, Josh.
因为你们太棒了嘛
Uh, yeah, 'cause you guys were so great.
我是独舞
I danced alone.
下一议程
Next order of business,
丽萨想在她院子里挖个护城沟
uh, Lisa would like to put in a little moat in her yard.
配一个开合式吊桥
Aww, and with a drawbridge
从人行道直达前门
from the sidewalk to the front door.
我从小就有个公主梦
I've always dreamed of being a princess.
大家同意吗
All in favor?
-爱[同意] -"哎"哟妈呀
- Aye! - Eyesore.
克莱尔 你说什么了吗
Claire, did you say something?
抱歉 你们就这么通过了丽莎公主的申请
I'm sorry. You're just gonna rubber-stamp Princess Lisa here,
但我却不能在自家后院盖女人窝吗
and I can't have a She Shed in my backyard?
你能等轮到你时在说吗
Could you please wait your turn?
我们还没到新议题呢
W-We haven't moved on to new business yet.
行 申请讨论新议题
Fine. Motion to discuss new business?
附议 准许克莱尔·邓菲发言 感谢你
Seconded. Recognizing Claire Dunphy. Thank you.
我拿到我的许可之前是不会走的
I'm not leaving here until I have my permit.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
我投递了搭建一个简单建物的申请
I submitted a request to build a simple structure
从街上看不到 不影响景观
you can't even see from the street.
说到影响 为什么没有人
Speaking of which, why is nobody sounding the alarm
给盖里的前卫邮箱踩刹车
over Gary's avant-garde mailbox?
-形状就是个鸡鸡啊 盖里 -宝贝
- It's a penis, Gary. - Honey.
干嘛 什么 你来这里干嘛
What? What? Oh! What are you doing here?
我还打算问你这个问题呢
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
抱歉打扰了 请继续你们的出色工作
I'm so sorry to interrupt. Keep up the great work.
同志们真是辛苦了
It couldn't have been easy
不让下水道鳄鱼新闻流出 造成恐慌
keeping that sewer gator under wraps.
哪有什么鳄鱼
What alligator?
这样是不对的
No, that.
就是这样 这不公平啊
See that? That's not fair.
就因为我不是你们业主协会邪教的一份子
Just because I'm not part of your little cul-de-sac cult --
-你们这业主"邪"会 -这哏不错
- your little cult-de-sac -- - Oh, that was a good one.
我觉得大家懂你意思了 我们走吧
I think you made your point. Why don't we get going?
克莱尔 我们没听过你的女人窝啊
Claire, this is the first we're hearing about your She Shed.
那我这里有个东西给你们
Oh. Then I've got something for you right here.
她有枪
She's got a gun!
是一封信好吗 丽莎
It's a letter, Lisa --
印有业主协会字样的拒绝信件
a rejection letter on HOA stationery.
信件吗
Stationery?
为了减少树木砍伐
In the interest of saving trees,
我们所有的信件来往都是通过电邮
we do all our correspondence via e-mail.
走啦 克莱尔 我们不需要坐在这里
Come on, Claire, we don't need to sit here
听这些社区栋梁说的话
and listen to these pillars of the community.
那这封信是谁寄给我的
Then who sent me this letter?
还有谁知道我想搭个女人窝
Who knew I even wanted a She Shed?
有谁会在意这个呢
Who even...cared?
好啦
Okay.
小家伙 就是个直射
It's a straight shot, pal.
你能行 你感觉如何
You got this. How are you feeling?
我有点紧张
I'm nervous.
我儿子正在接受运动员的考验
My son was being tested as an athlete,
而我也在接受当父亲的考验
but I was being tested as a father.
我那一刻说的话将会影响乔人格的发展
What I said then would help shape the man Joe would become.
废物才会紧张
Nerves are for losers.
你现在的感觉是兴奋
What you're feeling is excitement
因为这是你人生第一次
because for the first time in your life
在做真正有意义的事情
you're doing something that actually matters.
其他的那些孩子 都想你怯场
These other kids -- they want you to choke
因为你是山丘之王 君临天下
because you're king of the mountain,
而他们也想爬上山顶
and they're climbing to reach you.
所以你得准备好踩掉他们登顶的手指
You've got to be ready to step on their fingers.
感觉好狠心啊
That sounds mean.
他们也会对你做同样的事
They would do the same thing to you.
去吧 拿下属于我们的荣誉
Now, get out there and take what is ours.
然后享受过程啊
And have fun.
这挺新鲜
Huh. That's new.
她就在我后面 她知道假信的事了
She's right behind me. She knows about the letter.
我们该怎么办 我们得想个解释啊
What are we gonna do? We have to think of an excuse.
我们没时间了
We don't have time!
她可能遇到红灯了
Huh. Guess she hit a light.
好吧 那我们来想想
All right. Well, let's think this through.
不是吧 菲尔 你就转身逃跑吗
Really, Phil?! You just turned and ran?
亲爱的 我...
Sweetheart, I...
-我 -你别想跑
- I... - Don't you run again.
好
Okay.
我只有一个问题 为什么
I have one question. Why?
一言难尽
It's complicated.
怎么一言难尽了
How is it complicated?
你印假的信纸 伪造一封信
You printed fake stationery and forged a letter
就为了让自己有个傻逼击球场
so you could have a stupid batting cage.
-这不是他的错 -卢克
- It's not his fault. - Luke --
我来告诉她
I'm gonna tell her.
-他害怕了 -什么
- He got scared. - What?
他害怕你以后
He thought you would like
会想整天泡在你的女人窝里
being out there alone in your shed so much
你不会想再跟他待在一起
you'd stop wanting to spend time with him.
怎么会
Come on.
他担心说不定你哪天就开始睡在里面
He was worried maybe you'd start sleeping out there.
很快那里就成了你与闺蜜们喝酒
Pretty soon it's where you and your friends go to drink
然后抱怨自己老公的地方
and complain about your husbands.
抱怨老公不需要个女人窝啊
Oh, I don't need a shed for that.
我们都是用手机群聊
We-we do it on a group text.
亲爱的 我都不知道你有这感觉
Honey, I didn't know that's how you felt.
你为什么不跟我说说呢
Why didn't you say something?
可能我不好意思露出内心的脆弱
I guess I'm not comfortable being vulnerable...
给除了卢克之外的人
...except-except with Luke.
我想盖那个女人窝的原因
The whole reason I wanted to get that shed
是给自己一个能静下心的地方
was to give myself a place to calm down
然后你也不用承受我像疯婆子
and spare you some of my insanity.
我本来还觉得这会让我们感情更好呢
If anything, I-I thought it would help our relationship.
亲爱的
Sweetheart.
他接受你的道歉
He accepts your apology.
剩下交给我就行了 兄弟
I got it from here, buddy. Mm.
我们得到了击球场 某种程度上吧
We got our batting cage... sort of.
妈 你觉得很快能轮到我跟爸上场吗
Hey, Mom, think we can get in there any time soon?
老娘今天这心情 别想了
Not after the day I've had!
走吧 兄弟 咱们明天再来碰运气
Come on, buddy. Let's try again tomorrow.
来啊
Come on.
爽
Yeah!
给
Here you go.
这什么鬼 我要推杆
What is this?! I need a putter!
放轻松嘛 落后一杆而已
Take it easy. You're only down by one stroke.
别提醒我
Don't remind me!
没事的 各位 他没事
He's fine, everybody. He's fine.
祝你好远 乔
Good luck, Joe.
歌洛莉亚 我猜你是来把乔拉回家的吧
Gloria? I-I guess you're here to pull Joey out of the tournament.
没没没 我是来给他加油的
No, no. I came to cheer him on.
不 我想过了你说的那些话
No, but I thought about what you were saying,
虽然你当时说得有些不对
and even though you weren't right,
但我还是决定按你说的做
I'm gonna let you have this one.
你可以的 宝贝
You can do this, baby.
别打扰我集中精神
I'm trying to concentrate!
这火气是怎么回事
What is that all about?
不知道啊 歌洛莉亚 你好像会让他紧张
I don't know, Gloria. You seem to make him tense.
-还有就是这个问题 -我就知道
- Uh, and there's this other thing. - I knew it!
你干扰了我的视线
You were in my eyeline!
别 乔 快回来
No. Wait. Joe, come here!
-我要踩了你的手指 -乔 快回来
- I'm going to step on your fingers! - Joe, come back here!
-我才是山丘之王 -把球杆给我
- I'm the king of the mountain! - Give me the club!
球杆给我
Give me the club.
快给我
Give me the club!
干嘛啊
Why?!
又来了
Not again.
曲棍球绝对是你的菜
You're gonna love hockey.
你知道吗
You know what?
如果我老家的人知道我来心理咨询师这里
If people back home knew I was in a therapist's office,
绝对会在我们当地杂志上的
it would be all over the "Rumors and Ramblins" section
"八卦漫谈"环节 大书特书
of the Grasshopper Gazette.
"自由左派西海岸毁了本地英雄"
"Liberal Left Coast Breaks Local Hero."
你在打什么字
What are you typing?
你刚才说的每一字每一句
Exactly what you just said,
别担心 是我的咨询要用 不是你的
but don't worry, it's for my therapy, not yours.
是啊 这的确是你的咨询
You know what? This is your therapy,
我也不想在这里
and I don't want to be here.
别这样 小卡 你也需要这个
Cam, come on. You need this.
你就试一次嘛 行不
Just give it a shot. Come on!
你好啊 米奇尔
Hello, Mitchell.
你好 格林医生
Hi, Dr. Green.
谢谢您特别空出时间来见我们
Thank you so much for making the time to see us.
好吧 你那是什么声音
Okay, what's that voice?
你是在试着压抑
Are you tamping down your
-自己的神经病来让你的医生夸你吗 -没啊
- crazy to impress your therapist... - No. No.
就像你在家政女佣来之前 先打扫一遍一样
...like you do when you clean up before the housekeeper comes?
感谢你的这些话
I appreciate what you're saying,
我听到了 我会好好想想
I hear you, and I'm gonna give it some thought.
什么鬼 我们能搬来这里住吗
The hell? Can we move into this place?
-你一定是卡梅隆吧 -是的
- You must be Cameron. - Yes.
很高兴跟你见面 我听过好多你的事
So nice to meet you. I've heard so much about you --
米奇尔 你对现在自己的举动有什么看法
Mitchell, how do you feel about how you're behaving right now?
不是太满意 我能重来吗
I don't love it. Can I-Can I restart?
好的
Okay.
好的 这个嘛
A-All right. Um, you know what?
这个... 这... 我不想在这里
This -- This -- I don't want to be here.
这不适合我
This just isn't me.
墙上的画好奇怪
The art on the wall is weird.
糖果感觉像是心理测试
The candy bowl feels like a test, uh...
这样吧 我要吃 就吃一个吧
You know what? I'm gonna have, uh, just one.
不要 我要吃全部
Nope. I'm gonna have all of them.
不对 我要走了
Nope. I'm just gonna leave.
小卡 跨出第一步最难 但值得你尝试
Cam, the first step is the hardest, but it's worth it.
家庭的问题需要时间来修复
It takes time to work through family issues.
她说的对 有些人花了一生时间
Yeah, she's right. Some people spend their whole lives
在试着解决这些问题呢
trying to resolve these things.
那我... 那我跟她说什么啊
What would I -- What would I even say to her?
我爸跟一个小镇公交女跑了一年
That my dad left for a year with the town floozy
我还以为那年他是去打仗
and I thought he was off being a war hero
我就像个傻逼一样
and that I'm an idiot
而且我永远不会原谅他
and-and that I'm never gonna forgive him?
我才不管他最后又回归家庭了呢
I don't care that he came-came back to us.
他骗了我 他让我从小到大都以为
He lied to me, and he let me grow up thinking my mama
我妈妈是他在世上最珍重的人
was the most important thing to him in the world.
他就是个骗子
He's a phony.
但或许... 他尽力了
You know, maybe, you know, he did do the best
用他会的那种方式
he-he knew how, you know?
他总是让我觉得安全与开心
He always did make me feel safe and-and happy.
或许他只是想保护我
Maybe he was just trying to protect me,
因为他的确是全心全意爱着我
because he did love me with all of his heart,
而且我感觉自己了解了他
and, actually, I feel like I know him,
比以前更了解 更爱他
like, even better now and love him even more.
是我的经历造就了我
I am the person I am because of all my experiences.
而我爱我自己
And I like me.
为此 我得谢谢我爸爸
And I have a daddy to thank for that.
感觉舒畅了好多
Hey! That felt great.
天啊 感觉被治愈了
Oh, my gosh. I feel healed.
很好的开始 但心理咨询...
Yeah, well, it's a good start, but therapy really is a --
不不不不不 太厉害了
No, no, no, no, no, no. That was extraordinary.
我从来没有见过像这样的
I have never seen anything like that.
他不需要我
He doesn't need me.
给
Here.
吃颗糖 祝你幸福
Have a hard candy and a good life.
等等 他完事了吗 不行
Wait, wait, wait, wait. He's done? No, no.
我 我来这里看十年了
Okay, I have-I have been coming here for 10 years,
而我还不得其门而入
and I am just barely scratching the surface.
而你夸他太厉害了
You call him extraordinary.
而我呢 我每周都来这里掏心掏肺
Meanwhile, I've been pouring out my soul to you every week,
而我得到的反应只有... 什么都没有
and I get -- boop -- nothing.
米奇尔 我有空出一小时时间
Mitchell, I did clear out the full hour.
如果你想要...
If you'd like to --
那就最好不过了 医生 太感谢你了
That would be great, Doctor. Thank you so much.
我很乐意
I would love that.
小卡 我们回家见 行 行
Cam, I will see you at home. Okay, okay.
-你选了正确的那个 -我在等着呢
- You chose the right one. - I'm waiting!
你可真会躲啊 小家伙
You sure know how to hide, buddy.
我到处在找你呢
I'm looking everywhere.
不对 不在台球桌底下
Nope, not under the pooltable.
你到底能躲在哪里呢
Where or where could you be?
曼尼 我很忙
Manny, I'm very busy.
不能之后再说吗
Can't this wait?
我等了10年了 别想躲 坐下
I've waited 10 years. This is happening. Sit.
我在看东西呢
Hey, I'm watching something.
是的 请看
Yes, you are!
带来演出"丝带狂想曲"
Presenting "Rhapsody in Ribbon."
找到你了 换我去躲
You are it. I'm hiding.
一
One.
二
Two.
三
Three.
四
Four.
五
Five.
六
Six.